A Guide to the Sealantic Fund Records FA265
Rockefeller Archive Center
Sealantic Fund records
1940-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Sealantic Fund, New York
FA265
48 Cubic Feet
Scope and Content
SOME MATERIALS ARE CURRENTLY RESTRICTED DUE TO PRESERVATION CONCERNS, AS NOTED.
The objective of the Sealantic Fund was to serve as a special purpose, grant making foundation. While the fund donated money for a variety of purposes, its most significant effort was in the furthering of the education of the American Protestant clergy. The importance of theological education at this time was heightened due to the recent conclusion of World War II.
Although the advancement of theological education was the central component of the Sealantic Fund, attention was also paid to historical preservation in Westchester County, NY. Following the shortage of competent nurses after World War II, the education of nurses in America also became a central issue to the Sealantic Fund.
The collection spans from the early 1940s to the later 1970s, following the merger of the Sealantic Fund into the greater Rockefeller Brothers Fund.
Related Archival Material
1. Rockefeller Family The Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller, Series N: Religious Interests The Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller, Series E: Cultural Interests Nelson A. Rockefeller papers, Series L: Projects 2. Rockefeller Brothers Fund 3. Rockefeller Foundation RG 1.2, Projects, Series 200.R: United States- Humanities and Arts
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Source of Acquisition
The Rockefeller Brothers Fund deposited the records of the Sealantic Fund at the Rockefeller Archive Center. The RAC received the collections in several accessions in 1979.
Conditions Governing Access
The Sealantic Fund records are open for scholarly access. SOME MATERIALS ARE CURRENTLY RESTRICTED DUE TO PRESERVATION CONCERNS, AS NOTED.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Institutional History
The Sealantic Fund (SF), one of the lesser known philanthropies of John D. Rockefeller, Jr., was established annd funded in 1938 to serve as a special purpose, grant making foundation. Although seemingly referencing a maritime corporation, the term Sealantic stems from a purpose dear to the heart of early Rockefeller generations: theology. The name arose from a combination of two churches located in the primary residences of JDR, Jr.--Seal Harbor, Maine ("seal") and Pocantico Hills, New York ("antic"). As its name references, the SF was not a private institution, but rather a fund used to support a variety of philanthropic purposes.
The SF was incorporated on November 19, 1938 in New York City. On the day of its incorporation, JDR, Jr., who was neither an incorporator nor a trustee, gifted 300 shares of Socony-Vacuum Stick (worth $3,637) to SF--a gift he contributed annually until his death. When he cerated the foundation, JDR, JR. stated that his prime purpose in establishing the fund was to provide over a period of years continuing support of the Pocantico Hills Union Church and the Mount Desert Larger Parish in Tarrytown, New York and Mount Desert, Maine respectively. In addition, JDR, Jr. ordered that the SF carry out any other philanthropic work that he believed deserved monetary support.
Although the SF accomplished a variety of purposes throughout its thirty-five year history, its most significant effort was a program created to further the education of the American Protestant clergy. This program would shape the existence of Protestantism in America after World War II. Following the tendency of the Rockefellers towards religious interests, another influential project began by the SF was the creation of America's first center for churches of numerous denominations. One important focus of the fund was that of historical restoration and preservation. The SF was responsible for dispersing funds for the restoration of numerous historic properties (specifically Sunnyside and Philipse Castle) in the Sleepy Hollow area of the Hudson Valley. The education of those both near and far soon became an issue. The SF chose to dedicate their time and money to enriching theological education abroad and nursing education at home.
The SF allowed JDR, Jr. to realize one of his oldest dreams: the agreement of Christian denominations in America to work together under one organization. JDR, JR., under the instrument of the SF, was financially responsible for creating the symbol of this unity--the building of the national headquarters (the Interchurch Center) on Riverside Drive.
The most substantial work during the existence of the SF occurred in the field of education, specifically in improving the education of Protestant ministers. Following a remarkable donation by JDR, Jr. of $20 million to improve the state of American Protestantism, the SF embarked on a thirty-five year reformation. It was decided that half of the donation would be used to further the existence of of six Protestant institutions--Vanderbilt, Univeristy of Chicago, Berkeley, Yale, Union Theological Semianry, Harvard--believed to be crucial to the strengthening of Protestantism. At this time, an additional $725,000 was donated to the American Association of Theological Schools because it was deemed necessary that the field of Protestant education have a central, professional organization to set and maintain standards. This substantial gift was followed, in 1957, by a gift to the International Missionary Council to fund the world's "younger churches" (those in Asia, Africa, and Latin America). This donation would culminate in the creation of the Theological Education Fund.
After receiving criticism for choosing only six seminaries to fund, the next move of the SF was to contribtue money to a range of seminaries, many of them less well known. This act helped to promote consolidation and mutual assistance in the seminary field. Following this announcement, SF received a letter from Morehouse University asking for support in the creation of America's first Theological education center composed of churches from numerous denominations. In 1959, the Interdenomiantional Theological Center was created. The success of the center led the SF to support further consolidation efforts, this time on America's West Coast. This new federation, the Graduate Theological Union, was formed in 1961 and was composed of five seminaries across California. After monitoring the Union for three years, the SS approved requests from the Graduate Theological Union to fund the creation of new facilities. Further donations were made to institutions modeled after the programs incorproated at the Interdenomiantional Theological Center and the Graduate Theological Union. The programs included the Boston Theological Institute, the Richmond Theological Center, and the Rochester Center for Theological Studies.
Once the SF felt that they had provided for American seminaries to the best of their abilities, their attention shifted to the basic component of providing ministers with a higher education. Approximately $5 million went towards the creation of fellowship grants administered under five separate program: Sealantic's Faculty Fellowships, the Protestant Fellowship Program, the Rockefeller Doctorial Fellowships Black Doctorial Candidates in Religion, the Parish Ministers Fellowship Program, and the Library Fellowship Program.
The final steps taken by the SF in Theological education was: first, the decision to provide the American Theological Library Association with a substantial grant, and second, the decision to fund the Case Study Institute. This last decision arose following the realization that many in the field believed that current educational courses were outdated--this institute was created to find a way to add innovation to the field of Theological education.
The SF contibuted to numerous organizations beyond the world of Theology. The most notable role of the SF outside Theological work was its use as a special instrument for the holding and operation of properties, ranging from a residence for young women on stage (the Rehearsal Club) to historically important properties such as Sunnyside. Sealantic's first substantial project outside Theology was the purchase and restoration of the Hudson River estate, Sunnyside--the home of Washington Irving, the first American Author of international fame. Following this purchase, the SF purchased two other properties which, alongside Irving's Sunnyside, made up Sleepy Hollow Restorations (on whose board many SF employees served). The conclusion of Sealantic Fund's connection with historical restoration was its purchase of Carter's Grove in 1964 (by 1969, the SF transferred ownership to Colonial Williamsburg).
A unique part of the SF history arose during the shortage of trained nurses in the mid-1950s and 1960s. The nursing program created by the SF ran from 1957 until 1970 (when it was taken over by the RBF). The significance of the program can be seen in the following three areas: their role in the growth of two-year college nurisng schools, and their support to registered nurses in receiving professional nurisng degrees and to students of disadvantaged minorities in entering nurisng schools. In the eyes of the SF, the creation of this program was a response to a crisis where private money was required. It was considered to be solely in the fields of education and social welfare.
The SF merged with the Rockefeller Brothers Fund in 1971.
- Miscellaneous: A-AL, 1955-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted from scholarly access due to preservation concerns.
- Miscellaneous: AM-American E, 1955-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous: American F-AMI, 1951-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American Theological Library Association: Library Manuscript, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Andover Newton Theological School, 1955-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Andover Newton Theological School, 1965-1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Andover Newton Theological School: Consultation on Continuing Education for the Ministry, June 1965 15-18 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous: Applications for Employment, 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous: AN-AR, 1955-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Asbury Theological Seminary, 1956-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous: AS-AZ, 1955-1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bureau of Social Hygiene, 1931-1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous: B-Berg, 1955-1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous: Berh-BEZ, 1955-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous: BF-BI, 1955-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous: BJ-BN, 1955-1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous: BOA-BOZ, 1955-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous: BP-BZ, 1955-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous: C-CARS, 1956-1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous: CART-CELL, 1955-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Center for Advanced Studies in Religion and Science, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous: Center A-Central, 1958-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous: CHA-CHI, 1955-1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Chicago Theological Seminary, 1963-1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Christian Theological Seminary, 1956-1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Christian Theological Seminary: Foundation for Religious Studies- Progress Report, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Christian Theological Seminary: Foundation for Religious Studies- Proposal and Progress Report, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous: CHR-CHU, 1955-1972 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Claremont School of Theology, 1962-1972 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Claremont School of Theology, 1956-1960 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous: CI-COLK, 1955-1972 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous: COLL-COLZ, 1955-1972 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous: COM-COT, 1955-1972 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous: COU-CZ, 1955-1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Miscellaneous: DA-DO, 1955-1973 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous: DR-Drew, 1956-1971 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Dubuque Theological Seminary, 1963-1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous: DU-DY, 1955-1972 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous: EA-EC, 1955-1973 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous: ED, 1958-1972 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Miscellaneous: EE-EM, 1955-1973 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Miscellaneous: EN-EU, 1955-1973 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Miscellaneous: EV-EZ, 1955-1972 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Miscellaneous: F-FI, 1955-1972 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous: FJ-FO, 1955-1971 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Foundation Library Center, 1957-1973 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous: FP-FR, 1955-1973 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Friends of the World Council of Churches, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Miscellaneous: FS-FZ, 1959-1973 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Fuller Theological Seminary, 1955-1973 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Miscellaenous: GA-GEZ, 1955-1973 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Miscellaneous: GF-GZ, 1955-1971 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Greenburgh Town, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Hartford Seminary Foundation, 1957-1972 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Miscellaneous: HA-HAZ, 1955-1977 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Miscellaneous: HB-HOU, 1955-1973 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Miscellaneous: HOV-HZ, 1952-1973 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Miscellaneous: IA-INR, 1956-1972 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Miscellaneous: INS-INTERB, 1954-1973 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Interchurch Center and Blaikie, Millers, & Hines Caterer and Cafeteria Management Agreement, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Interchurch Center and WM White & Sons Agreement, Undated (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Interchurch Center Nominating Committee: Appointments to Board of Trustees, 1958-1973 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Interchurch Center By-Laws, 1956-1961 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Interchurch Center: Carvings Proposed for Exterior on Riverside Drive, 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Interchurch Center: Committee on Organization and Operation, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Interchurch Center: Conference at Arden House, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Interchurch Center: Conferences, 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1963-1968 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1957 March-August (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1957 September-December (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Interchurch Center: General, 1948-1956 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Interchurch Center: Financial Statements, 1959-1972 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Interchurch Center: Laying of Cornerstone, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 78)
- Interchurch Center: Long Range Plan Committee, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 79)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Annual Meeting of Members, 1959-1973 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 81)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 82)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 83)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 16, Folder 84)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 85)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 86)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 87)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Minutes, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 90)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Board of Trustees Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 91)
- Interchurch Center: New York State Council of Churches, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 92)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Budget Committee, 1967-1973 (Box 18, Folder 93)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Building Committee Minutes, 1958-1969 (Box 18, Folder 94)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Executive Committee, 1960-1973 (Box 18, Folder 95)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Executive Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 96)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Operation Committee, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 97)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Operation Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 98)
- Interchurch Center Meetings: Operation Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 99)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 100)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 101)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 102)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 103)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 104)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 105)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 106)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 107)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee Minutes, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 108)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 109)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee Minutes, 1962-1965 (Box 22, Folder 110)
- Interchurch Center: Operating Committee Minutes, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 111)
- Interchurch Center: Plans for Expansion, 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 112)
- Interchurch Center: Plans for Expansion, 1957-1966 (Box 23, Folder 113)
- Interchurch Center Properties: Wood Property, 1962-1972 (Box 23, Folder 114)
- Interchurch Center Properties: 49 Claremont Ave. and 468 Riverside Drive, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 115)
- Interchurch Center Properties: 49 Claremont Ave. and 468 Riverside Drive, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 116)
- Interchurch Center: Special Document File, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 117)
- Interchurch Center Tax Matters, 1957-1971 (Box 24, Folder 118)
- Interchurch Center Tenancy Question, 1958-1972 (Box 24, Folder 119)
- Interchurch Center Tenancy Question, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 120)
- Interfaith Center: Metropolitan Theological Education, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 121)
- International Missionary Council, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 122)
- International Missionary Council, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 123)
- International Missionary Council, 1963-1965 (Box 26, Folder 124)
- International Missionary Council, 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 125)
- International Missionary Council, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 126)
- International Missionary Council, 1957-1959 (Box 26, Folder 127)
- International Missionary Council, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 128)
- Inter-Convention Committee on the Education of the Negro Baptist Ministry, 1952-1966 (Box 27, Folder 129)
- Miscellaneous: INTER-IZ, 1955-1972 (Box 27, Folder 130)
- Miscellaneous: JA-JZ, 1949-1972 (Box 27, Folder 131)
- Miscellaneous: KA-KZ, 1955-1973 (Box 27, Folder 132)
- Lilly Endowment, 1955-1966 (Box 28, Folder 133)
- Louisville Presbyterian Theological Seminary, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 134)
- Miscellaneous: LA-LZ, 1955-1972 (Box 28, Folder 135)
- Ministries Studies Board, 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 136)
- Ministry Studies Board, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 137)
- Minutes: Executive Committee of Sealantic Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 138)
- Minutes: Executive Committee of Sealantic Fund, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 139)
- Minutes: Executive Committee of Sealantic Fund, 1946-1949 (Box 29, Folder 140)
- Minutes: Executive Meeting of Sealantic Fund, 1950-1952 (Box 29, Folder 141)
- Minutes: Adjourned Annual Meeting- Members of Corporation and Trustees, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 142)
- Missionary Research Library, 1957-1966 (Box 29, Folder 143)
- Miscellaneous: MA-MB, 1948-1973 (Box 29, Folder 144)
- Miscellaneous: MC-ME, 1955-1971 (Box 30, Folder 145)
- Mount Desert Town, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 146)
- Miscellaneous: MI-NAS, 1955-1973 (Box 30, Folder 147)
- National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1958-1971 (Box 30, Folder 148)
- National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1955-1957 (Box 30, Folder 149)
- Miscellaneous: NA-NATIONAL H, 1955-1973 (Box 31, Folder 150)
- National Science Foundation, 1955-1967 (Box 31, Folder 151)
- Miscellaneous: NATIONAL I-NATZ, 1957-1970 (Box 31, Folder 152)
- Miscellaneous: NAU-NEW X, 1955-1973 (Box 31, Folder 153)
- Miscellaneous: NEW Y-NEZ, 1948-1972 (Box 31, Folder 154)
- Miscellaneous: NF-NT, 1955-1973 (Box 31, Folder 155)
- Nursing Papers, 1967-1973 (Box 32, Folder 156)
- Nursing Program: University of Alabama- School of Nursing, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 157)
- Nursing Program: University of Arizona, 1958-1967 (Box 32, Folder 158)
- Nursing Program: University of Arkansas- School of Nursing, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 159)
- Nursing Program: Background Information, April-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 160)
- Nursing Program: Background Information, January-March 1970 (Box 32, Folder 161)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 162)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 163)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 164)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 165)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, April-December 1966 (Box 33, Folder 166)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, January-March 1966 (Box 34, Folder 167)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 168)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers, 1952-1964 (Box 34, Folder 169)
- Nursing Program: Background Papers- News and Press Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 170)
- Nursing Program: Boston College- School of Nursing, 1958-1966 (Box 34, Folder 171)
- Nursing Program: Boston University- School of Nursing, 1958-1970 (Box 35, Folder 172)
- Nursing Program: University of Buffalo- School of Nursing, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 173)
- Nursing Program: University of California at Los Angeles- School of Nursing, 1958-1969 (Box 35, Folder 174)
- Nursing Program: Catholic University of America- School of Nursing Education, 1958-1970 (Box 35, Folder 175)
- Nursing Program: University of Cincinnati- College of Nursing and Health, 1958-1971 (Box 35, Folder 176)
- Nursing Program: University of Colorado- School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 177)
- Nursing Program: Columbia University-Teachers College, 1958-1971 (Box 35, Folder 178)
- Nursing Program: Cornell University- New York Hospital School of Nursing, 1967-1969 (Box 35, Folder 179)
- Nursing Program: Duquesne University- School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 180)
- Nursing Program: Emory University- School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 181)
- Nursing Program: Goshen College, 1966-1970 (Box 35, Folder 182)
- Nursing Program: Hunter College- Bellevue School of Nursing, 1958-1971 (Box 36, Folder 183)
- Nursing Program: Incarnate Word College- Department of Nursing Education, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 184)
- Nursing Program: Indiana University- Division of Nursing Education, 1958-1963 (Box 36, Folder 185)
- Nursing Program: Loyola University- School of Nursing, 1958-1969 (Box 36, Folder 186)
- Nursing Program: University of Maryland- School of Nursing, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 187)
- Nursing Program: National Fund for Graduate Nursing Education, 1959-1971 (Box 36, Folder 188)
- Nursing Program: National League for Nursing, 1954-1959 (Box 36, Folder 189)
- Nursing Program: National League for Nursing, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 190)